This area here, between the eyebrows, is a zone that indicates when someone truly
Questa zona qui, tra le sopracciglia, è una zona che indica quando qualcuno
is experiencing suffering,
soffre davvero,
or going through suffering in their life, whether it be physical, emotional, or otherwise,
o sta attraversando una sofferenza nella sua vita, che sia una sofferenza fisica, emotiva o altro,
you will observe this here, and in the eyes as well; you can perceive the eye almost making a movement, like this.
lo vedrete qui, e anche negli occhi, vedete l'occhio che fa quasi un movimento, così.
There is a specific geometry within the iris that can manifest in this manner, which...
C'è una geometria nell'iride che può manifestarsi, così, che...
It is also an initiation point that is also related
È anche un punto di iniziazione che è in relazione anche
with the...
con la...
The brain's primordium, at the outset, is flat.
La piega del cervello, all'inizio, è piatta.
And through the process of telencephalization, it undergoes this transformation.
E attraverso il processo di telencefalizzazione, fa così.
This is where the crista galli is established.
È qui che si forma la crista galli.
It is a point of concentration.
È un punto di concentrazione.
We call it the eye of clairvoyance.
Lo chiamiamo l'occhio della chiaroveggenza.
You have 'voyance'.
Avete la veggenza.
In this instance, one utilizes the other's emotions.
Lì, usiamo l'emozione dell'altro.
I will interact with your astral plane.
Giocherò con il tuo piano astrale.
And then, you have clairvoyance.
E poi, avete la chiaroveggenza.
That is to say, you begin to perceive the world entirely.
Cioè, inizi a vedere il mondo in modo completamente diverso.
from the perspective of the other. This implies perceiving their operational mechanisms. This, in itself, constitutes a form of clairvoyance.
dell'altro. Significa che vedi come funziona. Questa è già una chiaroveggenza.
This occurs here. And then, you have the third and unique form of 'voyance', which is polyvoyance.
Questo si fa qui. E poi, hai la terza e unica veggenza, è la poliveggenza.
You
Tu
begin to perceive God or this divinity in everything. You have
inizi a vedere Dio o questa divinità in ogni cosa. Avete
an electromagnetic spectrum.
uno spettro elettromagnetico.
This is what is perceived. You see, if I have developed, in fact, it
Ecco cosa vediamo. Vedi, se sono cresciuto, in realtà, non
is already quite significant. It is our rainbow
è già male. È il nostro arcobaleno
of light.
di luce.
However, observe what this represents as reality, you see, surrounding us.
Ma guarda cosa rappresenta come realtà, vedi, intorno a noi.
All that exists, all these frequencies; the more one enhances their capacities,
Tutto ciò che c'è, tutte queste frequenze, più aumenti un po' le tue capacità,
one can sometimes perceive phenomena slightly beyond the ordinary.
a volte puoi vedere cose un po' al di fuori.
The eye will receive luminous information; thus, it will receive a photon.
L'occhio riceverà un'informazione luminosa, quindi riceverà un fotone.
The very first layer that will be traversed will be the conjunctiva.
Il primissimo strato che verrà attraversato sarà la congiuntiva.
The second layer to be traversed will be the cornea.
Il secondo strato che verrà attraversato sarà la cornea.
The cornea, which is the anterior portion...
La cornea che è la parte...
...of the sclera, transparent.
della sclera anteriore che è trasparente.
Then, you will have the passage through the pupil.
Poi, avrete l'attraversamento a livello della pupilla.
So, the first chamber anteriorly is the anterior chamber,
Quindi, la prima camera anteriore è la camera anteriore
which contains aqueous humor.
che contiene l'umore acqueo.
The anterior chamber, the iris, with the pupil here, which
Camera anteriore, l'iride con qui la pupilla che
allows passage.
passa.
And here, you have a so-called posterior chamber,
E lì, avete una camera detta posteriore
which still contains the same fluid.
che contiene sempre lo stesso liquido.
But anteriorly here, you have what are called the ciliary bodies,
Ma qui davanti avete quelle che si chiamano le corcilari
which also produce [fluid].
che produrranno anche.
fluid, and slightly posterior here to what is called the limbus, you will find
liquido e un po' indietro qui da quello che si chiama il limbus avrete
the canal
il canale
of Schlemm, or scleral venous sinus, which reabsorbs [fluid]. So, there
di Schlemm o sclerotico che viene a riassorbire, quindi c'è
is continuously a fluid that
continuamente un liquido che
circulates here, which sustains and nourishes. Then it will traverse and encounter what is
gira qui che vive che nutre in effetti poi attraverserà e incontrerà quello
called the crystalline lens, responsible for accommodation. And at the level of the crystalline lens, the vitreous humor
che si
traverses to
chiama il cristallino accomodazione e a livello del cristallino l'umore vitreo
reach my
che attraversa per
retina, which is composed of different layers. So, not only do I perceive only a small light spectrum, but I am still capable of detecting the smallest possible quantity of light, called a photon. Furthermore, I have a constricted field of vision.
arrivare a livello della mia
I have a
retina che è fatta di diversi strati. Quindi non solo prendo solo un piccolo
possible vision, which is a centered vision, and I also have a very interesting vision, which is peripheral vision. I must learn to utilize these two types of vision. Thus, a frequency,
spettro luminoso, ma sono comunque in grado di prendere la più piccola quantità
a wave.
di luce possibile che si chiama fotone. Inoltre, ho un campo ristretto.
and a spectrum that, at maximum, varies in a foveal field of
Ho una
5 degrees,
visione possibile che è una visione centrata e ho anche una visione molto interessante,
c'est la vision périphérique. Je dois apprendre à utiliser ces deux visions. Donc une fréquence,
è la visione periferica. Devo imparare a usare queste due visioni. Quindi una frequenza,
une onde.
un'onda.
et  un  spectre  qui,  maximum,  varie  en  fétrade  de
e uno spettro che, al massimo, varia in fetrade di
5  degrés,
5 gradi,
in fact, even regarding 23 degrees, but I will explain that a bit later.
in realtà anche rispetto a 23 gradi, ma lo spiegherò un po' più tardi.
It is a 23-degree angle, like the orientation of your heart,
È un 23 gradi come l'orientamento del vostro cuore,
like the orientation of the Earth, like the orientation of your inner ears.
come l'orientamento della Terra, come l'orientamento delle vostre orecchie interne.
There are specific angulations within the body.
Ci sono angolazioni specifiche nel corpo.
This will reach the retina, initiating what is known as the phenomenon of transduction,
Andrà sulla retina, a fare quello che si chiama il fenomeno della trasduzione,
converting photons into electrical signals.
questo livello di fotoni in elettricità.
into a nervous impulse that will be transmitted to
in un flusso nervoso che sarà trasmesso a
the left and to the right,
sinistra e a destra,
for each eye, at the level of what is referred to as the LGN,
per un occhio ogni volta, a livello di quello che si chiama il CGE,
i.e., the lateral geniculate nucleus,
quindi il corpo genicolato laterale,
which will provide an interpretation, demonstrating how it integrates this information,
che darà un'interpretazione, come integrerà questa informazione,
parvocellular, koniocellular, magnocellular,
parvocellulare, cagnocellulare, maniocellulare,
which represent specific types of information.
che saranno informazioni specifiche.
Subsequently, once this process is complete...
Poi arriverà dopo, una volta che sarà...
It will then utilize what are known as the optic radiations to project towards the
Prenderà quelle che si chiamano le radiazioni ottiche per andare verso la
visual cortex, specifically above and below the calcarine fissure.
corteccia visiva, sopra e sotto la scissura calcarina.
This is very interesting and crucial to be able to localize.
Molto interessante, molto importante da saper localizzare.
This renowned journey, from the eye, encompassing all the interpretation we observe here,
Questo famoso viaggio, l'occhio, tutta l'interpretazione che vediamo qui,
and these radiations projecting towards these cortical areas and towards the various
e queste radiazioni verso queste aree corticali e verso i diversi
levels of interpretation.
livelli di interpretazione.
which we will now examine in a bit more detail.
che vedremo un po' più in dettaglio ora.